

Contact

L +84 333 583 800

vuvandinh203@gmail.com

Tp. Ho Chi Minh

Education

2021 - 2024

Ho Chi Minh City Industry and Trade College

Bachelor of Business Management

2018 - 2021

High school Le Quy Don - Da Teh

Bachelor of Business Management

Skills

F HTML

CSS

Javascript

React

Nodejs

Express

Language

Vietnamese

English

VU VAN **DINH**

Frontend developer

About Me

I am passionate about front-end development to create user-friendly websites. With I years of experience working with HTML/CSS, JavaScript and ReactJS, I have developed strong capabilities in these technologies. I pride myself on my ability to quickly learn new skills, work effectively in teams, and communicate well.

Experience

Website NFT Marketplace

4/2023 - 6/2023

Description: Electronic sales website, allowing users to log in,

post products for sale, buy online and make

electronic payments.

Technologies: ReactJs, Redux

Github: https://github.com/vuvandinh123/react_web_nft

Demo: https://vuvandinh123.github.io/react_web_nft/

Website Ecommerce

6/2023 - 1/2024

Description: Electronic sales website, allowing users to log in,

post products for sale, buy online and make

electronic payments.

Technologies: ReactJs, Tailwindcss

Github: https://github.com/vuvandinh123/laravel ecomm

erce_website

Activities

Join students who are good at website design

Throughout the competition, I actively engaged in conceptualizing, designing, and implementing innovative website solutions. Leveraging my expertise in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, I crafted visually appealing and functional websites that addressed specific project requirements.